WKCC AM广播电台 全天候为您服务
WKCC AM Talk Radio. All talk, all the time.
五点钟将为您带来体育和天气消息
Bringing you sports and weather on the five.
教会领袖谴责报复以及种族攻击...
Church leaders blame the rise of hate crimes and racially-motivated attacks...
...自称"Holnists"的民兵组织
...on a militia-like group calling themselves ''The Holnists. ''
这些组织中最激进最强大的一个...
One of the most radical and powerful of these groups...
...它的创始人著名的Nathan Holn发表声明
...claims as its founder, the famed motivational speaker Nathan Holn.
最后一个伟大的城市也消失了...
The last of the great cities died...
...在我父亲还是个孩子的时候...
...when my father was a child...
...也是另一场战争的牺牲品
...victims of yet another war.
他讲述了接下来的苦难历程...
He told of the plagues that followed...
...散落在各个小村落里的人们如何为了生存的希望...
...and how the living hid themselves, scattered in tiny hamlets...
...而互相残杀...
...in hopes of surviving whatever new madness...
...阴谋掠夺幸存的壮丁
...conspired to rob them of the little that remained.
在那些日子里，他一个人前行...
In those days, he walked alone...
...是那个混乱时代的孤独见证者
...a solitary witness to the chaos that reigned.
地球本身也已经残破不堪
The earth itself had fallen victim to the insanity.
他说有个冬天持续了三年...
He told stories of the 3-year winter...
...而脏雪却又不停的下
...and how the dirty snow never stopped falling.
他还看见了海洋 不孕、中毒、就快要死了
He saw the ocean, barren, poisoned, near death.
而人们就仰望苍穹16年...
And how they watched the sky for 1 6 long years...
...祈求这个伟大的地球的肺能够重新开始运转
...praying for the great lungs to start working again.
他说似乎海洋只能深深的一声叹息
He said it was as if the ocean had breathed a great sigh of relief.
许多来来往往的人们都放弃了他们的交通工具
Many commuters are abandoning their vehicles.
该死，Bill!
Goddamn it, Bill!
你知道我得先检查一下的
You know l need to check it first.
我不知道
l don't know.
比松脂要好些
Better than turpentine, Bill.
味道也差不多
Tastes about the same.
你说呢？
What do you say?
你叫一声阿
Your call.
你不会吹毛求疵的，Bill
You ain't picky, Bill.
我就喜欢你那样
l like that about you.
就像我喜欢我的屁股
Things l like about my ass...
...第一:
...number 1 :
有松脂也不错的
Will settle for turpentine.
我们找到个电视！
We got TV!
有147个频道
We got 1 4 7 channels, Bill.
我们搞清楚从耶稣...
We got everything from...
...到危险的每件事
...Jesus to Jeopardy .
比如...
''Like...
...沙子穿过沙漏 日子也如此
...sands through the hourglass, so are the days--.''
我们会观察的
We'll watch that.
...沙子穿过沙漏 日子也如此
...sands through the hourglass, so are the days of our lives.
"星期一"
''Monday.''
"星期一晚上"
''Monday night.''
星期一晚上足球
Monday-night football!
我可不想惹麻烦
l don't want any trouble.
我猜你也不想吧
l bet you don't either.
咱们和平解决吧
Let's just call it a draw.
我发财了
l'm rich!
我知道规则
l know the rule.
我的规则
lt's my rule.
不惜一切代价来避免文明
''Avoid civilization at all cost.''
我们得吃东西来，不是吗？
We got to eat, don't we?
把嘴张开
Open your mouth.
我们是还没有开始来做这些，但是...
lt's true we haven't done this for awhile but...
...看在上帝的份上 那就像是在骑自行车，Bill
...for God sakes, it's like riding a bicycle, Bill.
你有什么好担心的呢？
What are you so worried about?
你要做的不过是站在那里
All you got to do is stand there.
一切都尽在我的掌握
l'm the one with all the lines.
张开
Open up.
说"Awful"
Awful.
说"awful"就行了
Just awful.
他们说“别害怕，Macbeth...
They said, ''Fear not, Macbeth...
...自从Birnam Wood...
...till Birnam Wood...
...来到了到Dunsinane”
...comes to Dunsinane.''
我说...
l said...
“...自从Birnam Wood 来到了Dunsinane!''
'' ...till Birnam Wood comes to Dunsinane!''
谢谢
Thank you.
拿起武器
Arm yourselves!
Arm yourselves.
如果巫婆的话没错...
lf the witch's words are true...
...它就不会跑，乖乖呆在这！
...there'll be no running, hiding here!
他们会反抗...
They'll fight...
...就如同我们最后一顿饭就靠它了
...as if our last meal depended on it.
明天....
Tomorrow....
And tomorrow....
明天
Tomorrow.
还有后天
And the day after that.
短小的蜡烛就将熄灭
Out, brief candle!
生命不过是个行走时的影子...
Life's but a walking shadow...
...一个可怜的演员...
...a poor player who struts...
...在舞台上消磨时光...
...and frets his hour upon a stage...
...再也听不见
...and is heard no more.
这个故事的作者是....
lt's a tale told by....
ldiot.
一个低能儿...
A moron...
...只会大吵大闹...
...full of sound and fury...
...其实...
...signifying...
...什么也没说
...nothing.
但是狂风啊，你刮吧
But blow, wind!
灾难，你来吧
Come, wrack!
至少我们将会...
At least we'll die...
...战士战死沙场
...with the harness off our back!
我要和他谈谈
l want to talk to him.
孩子们以前从没见过莎士比亚
The children have never seen Shakespeare before.
他们现在也还是没见过阿
They still haven't.
谢谢你，你真是好人
Thank you. You're very kind.
我鼓掌是因为你身上发出臭味
l'm clapping because you stink.
Larry!
我想你还没搞明白是怎么一回事
l don't think you know how it works.
当我年轻时我也想当演员，不过一塌糊涂
When l was young, l tried to be an actor. l was awful.
但现在我不用担心我是最差的了
But now l won't die thinking l was the worst one.
-别说了 -没关系
-Stop it! -That's all right.
门票花了你多少钱？
How much did you pay to get in?
那就来咬我好了
So bite me.
你演的很好
You were very good.
-值不值得来点吃的？ -当然了，我们还有些汤
-Good enough to get something to eat? -Yes, we have some soup.
该死，是Holnists！
Holnists. Goddamn!
这些混蛋近来不杀人了
Bastards hardly kill anyone lately.
我们给他们些食物和物品
We give them food and supplies.
所有的镇子都这么做的
All the towns do.
我只是不想给他们我的任何东西
l'd just as soon not give them anything of mine, thanks.
你们在那里干吗？
What are you doing there?
你们在干吗？
What are you doing?
这只是个游戏，Bethlehem将军
lt's just a game, General Bethlehem.
是他们在戏里看到的一些东西 没什么伤害的
lt's something they saw in a play. No harm in it.
等等
Wait a minute!
一出戏？
A play?
表演给我看看
Show me.
没事的，孩子们，表演给我看看
lt's all right, children. Show me.
拿起武器
Arm yourselves.
不须跟着女巫跑
No running from the witches.
莎士比亚？
Shakespeare, is it?
真遗憾，我错过了一出好戏
l'm sorry l missed it.
我们几乎没有准备好我们想玩的游戏
We haven't nearly stocked the game that we thought we would.
是吗？ 但你们却有时间演戏？
Really? But you had time for a play?
我要从每个镇子...
l'm taking 3 conscripts...
...征召三名士兵
...from each town!
他们将会很荣幸的为Holnist军队效劳...
They will have the honor of serving in the Holnist Army...
...直到我认为合适的时机为止
...until such time as l see fit!
3个男人
3 men.
能不能做到？
Could you do that?
队长
Captain!
所有的男人...
All men...
...从15岁到50岁...
...between 1 5 and 50...
...有着适当的信仰基础的 现在请自我展示
...and of suitable ethnic foundation are required to show themselves now!
将军
General.
不用了，替我留着
No, but keep that.
接受
Acceptable.
长官？
Sir?
接受，队长
Acceptable, Captain.
你得多吃肉，不过我欣赏你的头脑
Need some meat on you, but l like an impressionable mind.
接受
Acceptable.
蒙古人
Mongoloid.
不要
Unacceptable.
我需要纯种的
l want pure blood.
就像....
Someone....
-别挥手 -大家看着我
-Don't wave. -People, you will look at me!
就像....
Someone like....
就像那个人！
Like that man!
你误会了
You don't understand.
你必须展示你自己
You were required to show yourself.
我不是他们一起的 我只是路过此地
l'm not with them. l'm just passing through.
把这家伙带走
Take the mule.
走，快走
Let's go! Move!
在这里
Ten-hut!
呈一字形排开
l want a line right here.
先生们，欢迎开始你们的新生活
Welcome, gentlemen, to your new life.
你们在Nathan Holn联军里获得了新生
You have been born again as soldiers in the United Army of Nathan Holn.
上帝度假去了
God rest his soul!
强壮的男人们已经被...
The strong have been sapped...
...软弱的哀号溶化了
...by the whimpering propaganda of the weak.
男人们...
Men...
...强壮的男人们 要反抗这种命运
...strong men, have been denied their destiny.
你们已经从那种命运中被解救了出来
You men have been saved from that fate.
赎金...
Redemption...
...就掌握在你们的手上
...is within your grasp.
你
You.
在获得这个机会之前你是干什么的？
What did you do before you were given this opportunity?
我有把铁铲，我挖洞
l had a shovel. l digged holes.
你挖洞
You digged holes.
现在你得把洞都填满了
Now you'll fill them.
你呢？
And you?
我？
Me?
你难道看不出来我是在和你说话吗？
ls there any question in anyone's mind that l was speaking to you?
就是你
Yes, you.
我只是个演员
l'm just a performer.
比如莎士比亚的戏剧
Shakespeare. Stuff like that.
莎士比亚？
Shakespeare?
他是个作家
He was a writer.
这个我知道
Yes, l know.
我知道莎士比亚是谁
l know who Shakespeare was.
高喊着Havoc!...
''Cry 'Havoc!' ...
...让战争带来的伤害...
...and let slip...
...成为过去！
...the dogs of war.''
我？
Me?
“做还是不做
''To be or not to be:
着是个问题”
That is the question.''
“我们很少...
''We few...
...我们很少开心...
...we happy few...
...我们这帮兄弟们''
...we band of brothers!''
“现在通过约克之光，我们要...
''Now is the winter of our discontent made glorious summer...
...把不满的冬天变成灿烂的夏天”
...by this sun of York.''
你相当不错
You're pretty good.
你也是个斗士 我可以从你的眼神里看出来
You're also a fighter. l can see it in your eyes.
你是个危险人物
You are a dangerous man.
你不同意？
Don't you agree?
长官，我不是不尊敬你 不过你最好还是把我放了
No disrespect, sir, but you'd be better off letting me go.
把我逼上绝路我就是个斗士
A fighter is about the last thing that l am.
难道你不认为这由我来决定吗？
Don't you think l should be the judge of that, soldier?
起来
Get up.
我说起来
l said, get up!
你说的没错 你不是个斗士
You're right. You're not a fighter.
但你将会成为一个斗士
But you will be.
我给你个机会...
l'm giving you a chance at a life...
...让你的生命有意义
...that means something.
值得好好过的生活
A life worth living.
-我很高兴看到你们 -我们很想你
-I'm glad to see you. -We missed you.
-我也想你们，你还好吗？ -我饿了
-I missed you. Kurt, how are you? -Hungry.
-Gretl,你的手指怎么了？ -被抓过
-Gretl, what happened to your finger? -It got caught.
-被什么抓过？ -Friedrich的牙齿
-Caught in what? -Friedrich's teeth.
谢谢
Thanks.
我赢了吗？
Did l win?
我想要告诉他
l tried to tell him.
再说一遍
Say it again.
说什么？
Say what?
你在镇上说的那些话
Words you said in town.
关于刮风还有其它 再说一遍
About the wind blowing and the rest. Say it again.
狂风你刮吧 灾难你来吧
''Blow, wind. Come, wrack.
至少我们将会战士战死沙场
At least we'll die with the harness off our back.''
那是什么意思？
What's it mean?
要么自由的活着
''Live free or...
要么死去
...die.''
我想
l think.
你们要么看电影要么就睡觉
You're going to watch a movie or you can sleep!
但是明天...
But tomorrow...
...你们要穿上制服...
...you run in uniform...
...背满包裹...
...full packs...
...跑20里路
...20 miles!
每个人都得做到...
Everybody makes it...
...否则大家都没得吃...
...or nobody eats...
...第三天排成队
...for the third day in a row!
大家都起来
Everybody up.
晚上有饭吃
You got meat tonight.
你为什么不告诉莎士比亚它有多和蔼？
Why don't you tell Shakespeare what kind it is?
骡子
Mule.
该死的动物
God-awful animal.
马和驴子杂交的东西
Sterile offspring of horse and donkey.
你能想象吗？
Can you imagine that?
在这个新世界里，没有那种混蛋的空间
There's no room in the New World for a bastard like that.
排在最后面的人肯定是还不很饿 所以没有吃的
Any man last in line ain't hungry enough to eat.
你排在最后面...
You show up last...
...所以你没得吃
...you don't eat!
我要是还排在最后一个我就去死
l'm going to die before l'm last in line again!
他们求之不得呢
That's what they're hoping for.
闭嘴！至少你还在吃！
Shut up! At least you're eating!
你当真？
You serious?
不错
Good.
真不错
This is good!
你想要这个？！
You want this?!
这就是你想要的？
This is what you want?
孩子们！
Babies!
这些山，因为有了音乐
The hills are alive
而充满了生机
With the sound of music
这将会是我生命中最美好的年月
These were supposed to be the best years of my life.
先生们，八大法律
The Laws of Eight, gentlemen.
那是由Nathan Holn传下来的遗产
That is the legacy handed down to us by Nathan Holn.
将永世长存
May he burn in hell.
这些是我们赖以生存的法宝
These are the laws that we live by.
8...
The 8...
...就是我们的象征
...is our symbol.
每个人都将自豪的遵守
Each man will bear it with pride.
那样你们才能成为我们帮派的一员
Only then will you be part of the clan.
先生们，请坐
Sit down, gentlemen.
第一条：
Law One:
你们必须无条件的服从命令 我叫你们坐下
You will obey orders without question. l told you to sit.
椅子不够
There weren't enough chairs.
我没说一定要坐椅子，你们可以坐在地上
l didn't specify chairs. You could've sat on the ground.
你们不执行一个明确的命令...
You disobeyed a direct order. You broke...
...你们违背了第一条
...Law One.
第二条：
Law Two:
惩罚会很迅速
Punishment shall be swift.
第三条
Law Three:
仁慈...
Mercy...
...是给弱者的
...is for the weak.
第四条：
Four:
恐怖...
Terror...
...必将战胜理性
...will defeat reason.
第五条
Five:
你们要效忠帮派
Your allegiance is to the clan.
第六条：
Six:
公平会得到体现
Justice can be dictated.
第七条
Seven:
每个帮派内的兄弟都可以挑战老大的地位
Any clansmen may challenge for leadership of the clan.
有没有人想向我挑战？
Does anyone wish to challenge me?
起立
On your feet.
第八条：
Law Eight:
只有一项惩罚，死！
There's only one penalty. Death.
求你了，求求你了
Please! l'm begging you!
在这里，有付出就会有回报
You will get out of this army what you put into it.
你工作你就会有得吃
Work and you'll be fed.
你战斗你就会被人所尊敬
Fight and you'll be respected.
你战死你就会被人所怀念
Die and you'll be remembered.
你想着要挑战我的老大地位？
You thinking of challenging for leadership?
我没有，长官
No, sir.
我只是个跟随者...
l'm a follower...
...而不是领导者
...not a leader.
你倒是挺伶牙俐齿的...
You got a smart mouth...
...莎士比亚
...Shakespeare.
你知不知道Getty上校一直追随着将军？
You see Colonel Getty always following the General?
但他最后却向将军挑战
He was the last man ever to challenge.
战斗持续了6秒...
Fight lasted 6 seconds...
...但将军没有杀他
...but he didn't kill him.
只是割下他的舌头...
Cut off his tongue...
...再割下他的软蛋
...then he cut off his balls.
而老Getty从此就像只忠诚的狗一样追随着将军
And old Getty's been following him around like a dog ever since.
解散
Fall out!
将军没注意...
The General don't see it...
...但是我说你有反骨
...but l say you've got some nigger in you.
这些都是你的？
They're yours?
真是个独行侠阿？
A solitary man, aren't you?
用望远镜可以从远处观察生活，而Shakespeare...
Binoculars to watch life from a distance and Shakespeare...
...却是读生活而不过日子
...to read about it, instead of living it.
我无意冒犯你 但是你自己好像已经读过莎士比亚的...
No offense, but you seem to have read Shakespeare...
...作品
...yourself.
如果他想要上档次 而不是仅仅干些暗杀之类的...
lf he wishes to rise above mere thuggery...
...一个军事指挥官必须受过正规传统的教育...
...a military commander must be classically educated...
...哲学、历史甚至戏剧敏感性
...philosophy and history, even a sense of the dramatic.
你以为我在战前是干什么工作的？
What do you think that l did before the war?
你以为我是个军人？
Do you think that l was in the army?
我卖复印机的
l sold copying machines.
我是个销售员...
l was a salesman...
...却有着领导天赋 设计并秘密的执行...
...with the talent to lead men, devise and execute a battle plan...
...军事计划
...locked away inside.
要不是Nathan Holn的话 我现在还在卖复印机
lf Nathan Holn hadn't come along, l'd still be selling copying machines.
你能想象...
Can you imagine...
...被浪费的生命 你能想象浪费有多严重吗？
...the wasted life? Can you imagine the magnitude of that?
但是战争...
But war...
...给了像我这样的人一个机会
...war gives men like me a chance.
Here.
“奖杯总是名花无主的
''The prize is often left unclaimed.
我们必须鼓起勇气来...
We must have the courage to grasp it...
...因为未来总是偏爱胆大的人”
...for fortune always favors the bold.''
他总是激励着我
He always inspires me.
我对未来已经有了设计，一个总体规划
l have a design for the future. A master plan.
我需要个能干的军官来帮我实现
l will need able officers to help me carry it out.
你有这个才能
You have the intelligence.
如果你忠心...
lf your heart matches...
...你可以走得很远
...you will go far.
我们接下来几周再详谈
We'll talk more in weeks to come.
解散
Dismissed.
队长
Captain!
我们明天出发
We'll be moving out tomorrow.
利用望远镜作侦查
lssue those binoculars to a scout.
书呢，长官？
And the book, sir?
烧了它
Burn it.
出去
Quit moving!
怎么样？
What happened?
-怎么样，他怎么说？ -没什么
-What happened? What'd he say? -Nothing.
他有没有提到我?
Did he say anything about me?
没有
No!
-我要离开这里 -你在胡说什么？
-l'm getting out of here. -What are you talking about?
-逃跑！ -什么？！
-Escaping. -What?!
你有没有听过Saint Rose？ 在海岸边
You ever hear of Saint Rose? lt's on the coast.
-那是天堂 -我们做不到
-lt's a paradise. -We can't.
我们可以！
We could!
我们三人就能做到
Between the 3 of us we could.
我不行
l can't.
我喜欢这 我喜欢成为一份子的感觉
l like it here. l like being a part of something.
前去看看
Take a point!
有人射了一只狮子
Some of the men shot a lion.
他们爬进来灌木丛
They crawled into the thicket.
你们这些狗崽子赚了一顿阿
One of you dogs earned a treat.
就在那边
Over there.
那些人今天早上猎杀了一只狮子
Those men hunted a lion this morning.
在战前这里肯定是个该死的动物园
Must've been a goddamn zoo here before the war.
不管怎样第三个人得跟着过去
Anyway, a third man went in after it.
我们不知道他是死还是活
We don't know if he's alive or dead.
我需要个志愿者
l want a volunteer.
你们中的一个要跟过去
One of you is going in there after him.
我去
l'll go.
我猜个子大的不一定胆大阿
l guess size ain't a measure of courage.
不是吗？
ls it?
我不这么想，队长
l don't think so, Captain!
活着回来，你就可以吃烤狮子了
Come out alive, you get a lion steak!
也许在那你能找到你的Saint Rose
Maybe you'll find your Saint Rose over there.
你还在磨蹭什么呢，等着圣诞节吗？
What the hell are you waiting for, Christmas?
为什么停下来
Why are you stopping?
我找到他了
l found him.
他找到他了
He got him.
我们走
Let's go.
快走
Hurry up!
你还有只狮子要背呢
You still got a lion to bag!
你们都给我退后
You men get back in line!
-他在那 -快开枪射击
-There he is! -Shoot him!
跳进水里 如果找不到他
ln the water. Come back without him...
...你和另外一个人就会替他去死
...and you and another man will die in his place.
快走快走
Go! Go!
我会抓住他的
l'll get him!
走
Go!
不要
Don't.
让我走吧
Just let me go.
我不想加入你们的军队
l don't want to be a part of your army.
我的军队？
My army?
我喜欢你这么说
l like the sound of that.
我逮着他了
l got him!
对不起
l'm sorry.
你怎么...
How come...
...会这样...
...you wrecked it...
...对我呢？
...for me?
不是你死就是我活
lt's me or you.
什么？
What?
可以不这样的
lt doesn't have to be.
我们可以一起走
We can go together. You and me.
好小子！
Good boy!
Good boy.
抓住他
Get him.
够了
Finish it!
抓住他
Get him.
这就对了
That's it.
该死的，抓住他
Get him, damn it!
“战士战死沙场”
''No harness on my back.''
你在流血?
Bleeding?
嗯，容易流血的家伙...
Well, bleeder...
...你想着你的Saint Rose?
...you want your Saint Rose?
我会给你你的Saint Rose
l'll give you your Saint Rose.
你好吗？
How you doing?
这可没你的份
You shouldn't have.
有条好消息
Here's a piece of good news.
Jerry决定上学了...
Jerry's decided to go to school...
...去获得他的承包人证书
...to get his contractor's license.
好样的，Jerry
Good, Jerry.
而小Jimmy想告诉他爷爷他已经...
And little Jimmy wants his grandpa to know that he lost...
...掉了牙了
...a tooth.
谢谢你为了我而呆在那里
Thanks for being there for me.
“全体男人
''Turn-on's:
穿着制服”
Men in uniform.''
嗨，你们好...
Greetings...
...Pineview, Oregon.
你沿原路返回吧
You just head back the way you came.
Pineview不买任何东西 我们也不想听你罗嗦...
Pineview ain't buying and we ain't listening...
...而我们也不搞慈善活动
...and we don't give charity.
是吗？
Really?
伙计我有公务在身
Civilian, l'm on official business.
我得进去这座Pineview的小镇
l demand entry into the town of Pineview.
你他妈的都在胡说些什么？
What the hell are you talking about?
伙计，我在和你讲话阿
l'm through talking to you, buddy-boy.
去叫你们当家的来把门打开
Get someone with the authority to open this gate.
就是他
That's him.
我是Sheriff Briscoe 你是谁啊？
l'm Sheriff Briscoe. Who the hell are you?
我是美国政府的代表
l'm a representative of the United States government.
我由...
Authorized by...
...重建恢复国会417号令授权...
...Order 4 1 7 of the Restored Congress to reestablish...
...在ldaho以及...
...communication route...
...Oregon...
...in ldaho and...
...传递信件
...lower Oregon.
用英语说是什么意思？
What's that mean in English?
我是你的邮差
l'm your postman.
把枪递给我
Hand me your gun.
对不起 你得明白...
Beg your pardon. Understand that...
...阻止妨碍邮件违反了联邦法律...
...tampering with or obstructing the mail is a federal offense...
...Bolin法案要求你们给...
...and the Bolin Act requires that you provide...
...所有的邮差提供...
...all mail carriers with...
...休息地以及...
...sanctuary and...
...营养食品
...nutri-- Food.
给你三秒钟离开这里
You got 3 seconds to get out of here.
你知道承包人Jerry吗？
You know Jerry the contractor?
等一下
Wait a minute.
我从包里拿些东西出来
l'll get something out of my bag.
你数到一了吗？
Did you say one?
一
One.
“Paul Davis...
''Paul Davis...
...Pineview14号”
... 1 4 Pineview.''
从没听说过这个人 二
Never heard of him. Two.
“Lily May Reno, 林肯路16号”
''Lily May Reno, 1 6 Lincoln Road.''
三
Three.
“lrene March, 沿河路478号”
''lrene March, 4 78 River Road.''
他念的是我名字吗？
Did he say my name?
我是lrene March.
l'm lrene March.
有封信给你
l have a letter for you.
你读一下好吗？
Would you read it?
我肯定它是私人信件
l'm sure it's personal.
-读吧，总要有个人读 -我来吧，妈妈
-Please, someone has to. -l'll read it, Mom.
我们在投递旧的储存信件...
We're delivering old stockpiles...
...但我收到的都是全新的
...but l'll accept all new correspondence.
“亲爱的lrene: 很抱歉我没有写信
''Dear lrene: Sorry l haven't written.
每件事都变得很疯狂
Everything's so crazy.
奇怪的天气 食物短缺...
The strange weather, the food shortages...
...Nathan Holn农场主带来了所有这些麻烦
...that farmer Nathan Holn causing all that trouble.
这很难理解
lt's hard to understand.
David的家离军队很远
David's home from the army.
在他到那之前战争已经结束了，谢天谢地
The war was over before he even got there. Thank God for that.
我们会为圣诞节想你的...
We're going to miss you for Christmas...
...但是也许得等到来年
...but maybe next year.
奉上我所有的爱”
All our love, Donna.''
我姐姐...
My sister...
...住在Denver...
...in Denver...
...15年前的事了
... 1 5 years ago.
谢谢你
Thank you.
你真是天赐之物
You're a godsend.
救世主
A savior.
我只是...
l'm just...
...邮差
...the postman.
我在路上走了好一段时间了
l've been on the road awhile.
我可不可以找点吃的？
l could use a little something to eat.
可以，当然可以
Yes, absolutely.
还有其它的要求吗？
ls there anything else?
是的，还有
Yes, there is.
如果镇上有狗...
lf there are dogs in this town...
...当我在这里的时候你们得看好它们
...you'll have to leash them while l'm here.
邮差先生
Mr. Postman
嘿，邮差先生 看看，瞧瞧
Hey, Mr. Postman Look and see
如果有一封 一封给我的信
If there's a letter A letter for me
洗干净熨好了，先生
Cleaned and pressed, sir.
我挂在那边
l'll just set them over here.
一位女士把你的裤子改小了
One of the ladies took your pants in.
她认为你瘦了
She thought maybe you lost some weight.
谢谢
Thanks.
有人说过晚餐的事情吗？
Didn't somebody say something about dinner?
我会带你带你到Foster那里的
l'm supposed to take you to Foster's.
我叫Ford
My name's Ford.
Ford Lincoln Mercury.
我以前叫John Stevens 但我改名字了...
My name used to be John Stevens, but l changed it...
...因为我想开车
...on account of l want to drive cars.
这里是大家聚会在一起的地方
This is where everybody meet and gather.
你能不能给我们讲讲关于政府的情况？
Can you tell us about the government?
-告诉我们每一件事 -有没有总统？
-Tell us everything. -ls there a President?
有的
Yeah.
叫什么名字?
What's his name?
-你看，我已经非常俄勒 -来吧
-You know, l'm pretty hungry. -Come on.
请！
Please!
他的名字...
His name...
...叫...
...is...
...Richard Starkey
...Richard Starkey.
来自Maine.
From Maine.
他有句名言
He has a saying.
“形势会越来越好
''Stuff's getting better.
形势每天都在好转”
Stuff's getting better every day.''
他是共和党还是民主党？
ls he a Democrat or a Republican?
政党都已经消失了
Parties are over with.
他是独立当选的
lt's an individual that counts.
那欧洲怎么样了？
What about Europe?
欧洲？
Europe?
有没有消息？
Any word?
嗯，在冰岛...
Well, there's...
...空气非常不错
...good air in lceland.
Nathan Holn还活着吗？
ls Nathan Holn still alive?
他死了
He died.
皮肤癌
Skin cancer.
他可能死了...
He may be dead...
...但是Holnists怎么样了呢？ 政府都采取什么行动了？
...but what about the Holnists? What'll the government do about them?
政府还只是刚刚开始做准备
The government's just getting started.
所以你们要靠你们自己坚持6个、8个或者18个月
So you're going to be on your own for 6, 8 or 1 8 months.
海军陆战队怎么样了？
How about the Marine Corps?
安静
Be quiet.
大家安静
Everyone be quiet.
我们就不能让他好好吃吗？
Can't we just let this man eat?
让我们祷告吧
Let us pray.
感谢你给我们食物
We give you thanks for this food...
今天
...this day...
这个人还有他的好消息
...this man and his good news...
是你答应我们的
...evidence of your promise...
你将会把我们的国家团结在一起
...that you will hold our country together.
阿门
Amen.
跳个舞吧？
Would you like to dance?
我不知道我会不会跳
l don't know if l can.
我想我还只是初学
l think l'm still on duty.
你所要做的就是坚持住
All you have to do is hold on.
有很长时间了
lt's been a long time.
有什么不对劲吗？
Something wrong?
你多高？
How tall are you?
六尺高
About six feet.
你聪明吗？
Are you smart?
比有些人聪明吧，怎么了？
Smarter than some, l guess. Why?
只是随便问问
Just wondering.
你有没有得过腮腺炎？
Have you ever had the bad mumps?
从来没有
Never had the bad mumps.
也没有得过梅毒之类的病？
No syphilis, nothing like that?
据你所知...
So as far as you know...
...你精子质量不错？
...you have good semen?
你在开玩笑？
ls that a trick question?
不，我没有
No, it's not.
我只是问你...
l'm only asking...
...因为我想让你使我怀孕
...because l want you to make me pregnant.
好吧...
All right...
...这就对了
...that's it.
等等
Wait.
请等一等
Wait, please.
好像是个穿制服的
lt's got to be the uniform.
这是我丈夫，Michael 他没有反对
This is my husband, Michael. He hasn't said no.
我什么也没说
l haven't said anything yet.
我们连续三年一直都打算要个孩子
We've been trying to have a baby for 3 years.
我们不能指望他 他一岁时就已经的了腮腺炎
We cannot on account of Michael. He had the bad mumps when he was 1 .
所以我们需要一个捐精者
So we need a body father.
我们本可以在这里找一个 但这样会带来很多问题
We could ask a man here, but it may cause problems.
我们见到过这样的事
We've seen it happen.
在女人没表现出来以前都没问题 但之后就很麻烦了
Things go okay until the woman shows, then it can be difficult.
但是你只是路过这里发发信件
But you'll only be around once in a while with the mail.
你是个邮差
You're the postman.
你觉得怎么样？
What do you say, mister?
你得帮我们一个忙
You'd do us a favor.
我会考虑考虑
l'm going to think about it.
请原谅
Excuse me.
我妈妈想给你些东西
My mother would like to give you something.
妈妈，他就在这里
He's right here, Mom.
这是给我另外一个女儿的...
lt's to my other daughter...
...她叫安妮
...Annie.
信上没说她在哪
lt doesn't say where.
她五年前离开了这 我们不知道她在哪里
We don't know where she is. She left 5 years ago.
我们听说她住在北部
The last we heard she was living up north.
我说，March夫人 你应该知道--
Look, Mrs. March, you should know that--
知道什么？
lKnow what?
我对你有种直觉
l have a feeling about you.
我知道你会答应我的
l know you'll do what's right.
我得赶紧离开这鬼地方
l got to get out of here.
放松，宝贝
Easy, boy.
就在那个角落
lt's right around the corner.
什么东西？
What is?
你正在找的东西
What you're looking for.
我在找什么？
What l'm looking for?
疯狂的老白痴
Crazy old coot.
我就知道你会来的
l knew you'd come here.
是吗？
You did?
你是如何成为一个邮差的？
So how do you get to be a postman, anyhow?
在正确的时候你得出现在正确的地点
You have to be in the right place at the right time.
我怎么才能做到呢？
How can l do it?
-我还以为你想要开车呢 -不再想了，那时小孩子的玩意
-l thought you wanted to drive cars. -Not anymore. That's kid's stuff.
这是现实
This is real.
那正确的地点又在哪里？
So where's the right place?
你知道，可能在任何时间的任何地点
Could be anywhere, you know. Anytime.
只有另外一个邮差才能让你成为一个邮差
Only another postman can make you a postman.
就像吸血鬼那样？
lKind of like vampires, right?
对，有点像那样
Yeah, something like that.
你必须得发誓
You have to be sworn in, so....
邮局有些不太稳定，也许持续不了多久
The organization's kind of shaky right now. lt might not last.
怎么发誓？
What does?
你将会碰到一些根本不信任你的人
You'd meet people who don't believe in you.
我会和他们坦诚相待
l'll set them straight.
邮差是个孤独的工作
lt's a lonely job.
我这一生都孤独
l've been lonely all my life.
我也一样，Ford
So have l, Ford.
我也一样啊
So have l.
真该死！
What the hell!
你跟着我念
You repeat after me.
“无论大雪还是...
''Neither snow...
还是暴雨...
...nor rain...
无论是炎炎烈日...
...nor heat...
还是漆黑夜晚...
...nor gloom of night...
邮差...
...stays these couriers...
都会迅速的完成他们的任务”
...from the swift completion of their appointed rounds.''
好了，可以了
Okay, then.
不，我说可以了 你听就行了
No, l'm saying that. You just listen.
对不起
l'm sorry.
经过我的授权，现在你可以投递这些信件了
By my authority you're now empowered to carry the mail.
恭喜你
Congratulations.
你是个邮差了
You're a postman.
为了送信我会万死不辞
l'd die to get a letter through.
你说什么？
What did you say?
-我说，为了送信我会万死不辞 -Johnny!
-l said l'd die to get a letter through. -Johnny!
你怎么还不走开
Why don't you run along.
我要和他说几句话
l need to speak to this man.
我待会再找你
l'll see you around.
就这么说定了，Ford
Sure thing, Ford.
Johnny对你印象很好 整个镇子的人对你印象都很好
Johnny is impressed with you. Whole town is impressed with you.
我猜不包括你吧
l take it you're not.
-你比你看起来的要聪明的多 -有什么可以效劳的？
-You're smarter than you look. -What can l do for you?
要么你自己自动消失要么我把你赶走 两条路随你挑
You can either clear out or l can throw you out. Either way suits me.
你还没搞明白 我是由政府授权的--
You don't understand. l'm a government employee authorized by--
你被授权个屁！
You are not authorized by shit!
你只是逃难到了这里 你只不过是个...
You were trying to sneak out of here. You are nothing...
发现了一袋信件的流浪汉 我要你滚出我的镇子
...but a drifter who found a bag of mail. l want you out of town.
好吧，我会把这都写进我的报告
All right. This is going in my report.
邮差先生，这里的人们不需要梦想
These people don't need dreams, Mr. Postman.
他们需要一些实际的东西 他们需要Holnists的帮助
They need something real. They need help with the Holnists.
你能带给他们这些吗？
Are you going to bring them that?
我想不能吧
Didn't think so.
到目前为止你带给我们的只是 几碗汤还有几颗破碎的心
All you cost us so far is a few bowls of soup and maybe a few broken hearts.
我要这个地方保持原样
l aim to keep it that way.
你可以在这待到明天早上...
You can stay here till morning...
以后我就再也不想看见你了
...then l don't ever want to see you again.
Benning
''Benning.
Portland
Portland.
Boston？
Boston''?
这些家伙--
What the hell these people--
走开
Just leave it.
我叫你走开
l said, leave it.
Saint Rose？
''Saint Rose''?
你好，Abby
Hello, Abby.
你明天就要走了？
You'll be leaving tomorrow?
是吧
l guess.
每个人都在熬夜写信 等着你帮他们带走
Everybody's up late writing letters for you to take.
他们都很兴奋
They're so excited.
那你呢？你写信了没有？
And how about you? Do you have a letter?
我不知道要写给谁
l don't have anybody to write to.
我可以给你找个笔友
l'll find you a pen pal.
就是有着相同爱好的一些人
Someone with similar interests. You know?
比如说跳舞了，还有...
Like dancing and...
检查腮腺炎
...checking for mumps.
你很风趣
You're funny.
镇上的人几乎都不懂风趣了
Hardly anybody's funny around here.
你已经决定了没有？
Have you decided yet?
我一直都在考虑
Been thinking about it.
当然了
Sure.
我是说...
l mean...
为什么不呢？
...why not?
天啊，你真是太....
God, you're so....
你太...
You're so...
漂亮了
...beautiful.
对不起，也许你希望这更像是个医疗手术
l'm sorry, you probably want to keep things more clinical.
你甚至不知道我的名字
You don't even know my name.
我不想知道
l don't want to.
如果你把眼睛闭上的话...
lt would be easier for me...
我会觉得更自然
...if you closed your eyes.
邮差先生，我们经过讨论
We took a vote, Mr. Postman.
希望你能收下
We want you to have this.
所以你不能拒绝
So you can't say no.
我收下了
l'll take it.
一卷铺盖、一些麦片还有一周的干粮
You got a bedroll, some oats and a week's rations.
很好
Good.
谢谢
Thank you.
你要往哪里走？
Where will you go from here?
哪里？
Go?
西方...
West...
然后我又会再返回来
...then l'll work my way...
就像走个"8"字形
...back here, sort of a figure eight.
现在的情况是困难了点
Times seem hard right now.
但是你们要坚信会越来越好的
But you got to believe things are getting better.
鸟儿又开始迁徙了
Birds are migrating again.
雨季来临了
The rains are back.
局势...
Stuff's....
局势正在逐渐好转
Stuff's getting better.
Oh beautiful
For spacious skies
For amber waves of grain
该死
Shit!
无论你是谁 你还是显得有些紧张
You've got a hell of a nerve, whoever you are.
今天早上你看见Abby了吗？
Did you see Abby around this morning?
我就送你到这里了
This is as far as l go.
你自己上路吧
You're on your own.
God shed his grace on thee
And crown thy good
With brotherhood
你真的像你说的是个邮差吗？
Are you really who you say you are?
如果我带着信件回来...
lf l come back with some mail...
你就会相信了
...you'll know.
该死
Goddamn it!
你看什么？
What are you looking at?
全身
Everything.
他们通常不看我的
They don't usually look at me.
那个...
Who is responsible...
...是谁干的？
...for that?
我说...
l said...
...那是
...''Who's responsible...
谁干的？
...for that''?!
Holnists,Johnny 你得呆在--
Holnists, Johnny. You got to stay--
-你不能让他们发现 -我是个邮差！
-You got to stay out of sight. -l'm a postman!
我不会当逃兵的！
And l'm not running from anybody!
呆在这里 不然我会亲自把你锁起来！
Stay out of this, or l will lock you up myself.
你得负责
You'll be responsible.
去把旗子烧了
Now set that flag on fire.
从窗户扔进邮局
Throw it through the window of your post office.
快照办，Michael
Do it, Michael.
没事的，Michael，快照办
lt's all right, Michael. Throw it.
美利坚合众国...
The United States...
...并不存在！
...doesn't exist!
那面国旗就是垃圾
That flag is an abomination!
有一个最奇怪的小山羊 它躲在栅栏后面....
There was the strangest little goat and it was behind a fence and it....
我看着它而它脸色就变了
l looked at it and it had a color to it.
不错
Good.
都不错
Everything.
我很吃惊 难道它是....
l was amazed. lt was....
真不赖！
Good Lord!
先生们，那个...
That, gentlemen...
是第一流的美臀
...is a first-rate piece of ass.
去叫镇长给我引见一下 她这种美人不属于这种小地方的
Tell the sheriff to introduce me. She doesn't belong in this mudhole.
请原谅
Excuse me.
又是你啊
You again!
她是我老婆，将军
That's my wife, General.
她已经结婚了
She's a married woman.
是吗？
Really?
你知道我们在这里执行的是什么政府体制吗？
Do you know what system of government we have here?
我们执行的是所谓的联邦体系 就像中世纪那样
We have what is known as a feudal system, like in the Middle Ages.
君主和臣子 就像你和我
That's lords and vassals. That's you and me.
现在那些君主
Now those lords...
他们有些想法
...they had some ideas.
他们认为如果一个臣子结婚了
They believed that if a vassal got married...
那君主就有权...
...it was the lord's right...
有权...
...his right...
享有和臣子的新娘过夜的“初夜权”
...to sleep with the bride on the wedding night.
我和Abby已经结婚三年了
Me and Abby have been married 3 years.
真遗憾我没有被邀请参加你们的婚礼
l'm sorry, but l wasn't invited to the wedding.
你已经帮我一个忙了
You've already done me one favor, son.
不要让这件事成为你的一个污点
Don't let this be a black mark on an otherwise perfect record.
我们都是斯文人
We'll be civilized about this.
我希望你能祝福我
l want you to give me your blessing.
先生，我做不到
Sir, l can't.
你做不到？
You can't?
你做不到
You can't.
做不到
''Can't.''
我们曾有个伟大的国家
We had a great nation once.
我知道它为什么能伟大
lKnow what made it great?
因为“我做得到”
''l can.''
直到弱智们来了
Till the weak came along.
“我做不到”破坏了我们
The ''l can'ts'' destroyed us!
我现在就要让我们重新强大起来
l'm going to make us strong again.
我要成为一个新国家的...
l'm going to be the father...
...国父
...of a new nation.
你知不知道为什么...
And do you know why...
...会是我呢？
...it will be me?
因为“我做得到”
Because l can.
快住手
Stop it!
你杀死他了
You're killing him!
让我过去
Let me go!
求你了让我过去吧
Please, let me go!
帮帮他啊，谁能帮帮他啊
Help him, somebody! Please!
你大可不必--
You didn't have to--!
不必什么？
Didn't have to what?
你个混蛋！
You bastard!
是你杀了他
You killed him!
你的人好像很不安分阿
Your people seem seditious.
你好像也不安分
You seem seditious.
我看见的都是什么呢？
What am l seeing here?
我在等着呢！
l'm waiting!
有个人带着信件来过这 他说他是个邮差
A man came through with mail. Said he was a postman.
他说东部的政府已经重建起来了
Said that the government had been restored back east.
什么政府？
What government?
美国政府！
The United States government!
谁说的？
Who said that?
他往哪个方向走了？
Which way did he go?
不要让我再问第二遍
Do not make me ask again.
东边
East.
派一队人去东边
Send a patrol east!
再派三队人...
Send 3 more...
...去北边，南边和西边！
...north, south and west!
他们最好是在东边找到他
They'd better find him east.
快把那T恤脱了，Johnny!
Take that damn shirt off, Johnny!
我已经保护了这些信件
l managed to save these.
你也想死吗？
Do you want to die too?
我要带着这些信件去南方
l'm headed south with the mail.
别发傻了
Don't be a fool.
那我该怎么办？
What should l be?
Rachel Clark.
Charlie Sykes
''Charlie Sykes.''
Graham Drewitt
''Graham Drewitt.''
G.D在去年冬天得流感死了
G.D. died of flu last winter.
就这么多了
That's all there is.
伙计们，就这么多了
That's all there is, folks.
目前而已
For now.
将来会有更多的 只要有个邮局系统的存在
But there'll be more, lots more, once there's a real system in place.
对吧？
Right?
纽约城怎么样了？
What about New York City?
他们有没有从这场灾难中幸存下来？
Did they survive the plague?
幸存？
Survive?
他们修复了百老汇并重新开张了
They got Broadway up and running again.
还有个小孩演Andrew Floyd Webber 你肯定不敢相信
There's a kid doing Andrew Floyd Webber, you wouldn't believe.
发一封信要多少钱？
How much is it to mail a letter?
发一封
''Mail....''
他们不肯开城门
They won't open the gates.
他们说他们有个来自美国政府的代表
They say they got a representative of the Restored United States in there.
他们说我们的军队是非法的
They say this army is illegal.
-他们还说-- -快去死吧!
-And they say-- -Drop dead!
下地狱吧！
And go to hell!
他们就这么说的
That's what they say.
你们在干吗？ 快开城门
What are you doing?! Open the gates.
ldiots!
你都在想些什么？！
What're you thinking?!
《罗马书》上...
The Romans...
有句话...
...had an expression...
常被用来吓唬小孩子
...they used to scare their children.
“Hannibal...
''Hannibal...
...ad portas”
...ad portas!''
Hannibal...
...就在门口
...is at the gates.
你知道Hannibal是谁吗?
Do you know who Hannibal was?
当然不知道
Of course not.
像你这么漂亮的女孩当然不会明白这种事情了
A pretty girl like you wouldn't understand something like that.
-让我们和他们打吧！ -用什么打？
-Let's fight them! -With what?
我们有五把枪 却一发子弹也没有
We've got 5 guns, maybe 0 rounds of ammo.
就这些武器我们怎么和他们打？
How we going to fight with that?
你们不要打
You don't.
和他们谈判吧
Negotiate a settlement.
给他们些额外的补给
Give them extra supplies.
告诉他们，你是政府的代表
You're the government rep. Tell them.
就在这里
Right here.
快点 我还有个攻击计划要制定
Make it quick. l've got an attack to coordinate.
他们叫我来订个和平条约
They've asked me to negotiate a peace treaty.
我认识你吗？
Do l know you?
我不这样认为，先生
l don't think so, sir.
你就是邮差
You're the postman.
是吗?
Aren't you?
进去!
lnside!
美国的信
''U.S. Mail.''
重建后的美国
''The Restored United States of America.''
这里的人真的相信这些狗屎?!
Do these people really believe that shit?!
说真的，你到底是谁?
Who are you, really?
我是一个美国的邮差...
l'm a United States postman...
...通过重建的国会第417号命令授权
...authorized by Order 4 1 7 of the Restored Congress.
我参加了Georgetown战役 我亲眼目睹白宫被夷为平地
l was at the Battle of Georgetown. l watched the White House burn down.
你别想让我...
Do not try to sell me...
...相信那所谓的重建的美国!
...on any Restored United States!
新的首都建在Minneapolis...
The new capital is based in Minneapolis...
...在Hubert Humphrey的地下宫殿里面
...inside the Hubert Humphrey Metrodome.
你知道过去的维京人在什么地方玩耍吗?
You know where the Vikings used to play?
你在开玩笑吧
You're funny.
条件是什么?
What are the terms?
他们将打开大门, 给与平常双倍的物资...
They'll open the gates, give double the usual...
...只是...
...just...
...不要伤害任何人
...don't hurt anybody.
这一切只是一个误会
This was all a misunderstanding.
我赞赏你的提议,邮差先生
l appreciate your offer, Mr. Postman.
但事实是你根本没有资格来讨价还价
But the fact is that you're in no position to negotiate.
这里的人造成了疯狂和暴乱...
These people made it through the bugs and the riots...
...还有长达三年的冬天, 但是他们并不想让你幸存
...and the 3-year winters, but they're not going to survive you.
给我开火!
Fire at will!
法律第六条:
Law Six:
法律就是...
Justice can be...
...命令!
...dictated!
杀了他, 把重建的美国和他一起杀了
lKill him, and kill the Restored United States with him.
根据法律第8条...
ln accordance with Law 8...
...以及紧急事件授权第46号命令...
...and by the authority of Emergency Order 46...
...你将因此--
...you are hereby--
抓住她!
Get her!
快去, 抓住他!
Go on, get him!
我们现在不能停
We can't stop now.
你怎么了?
What are you...?
噢，上帝呀!
Oh, God!
趴下
Come on down.
别动
Don't move.
如果你有子弹,你早开枪了
lf you had a bullet, you'd use it.
快走
Come on.
我想我很久没喝过汤了
l don't think l ever had water soup before.
也许下次我们应该试着放点盐
Maybe next time we could try it with a little sand.
泥土
Dirt.
也许只是一点佐料
Maybe a twig garnish.
你总是认为我很好笑
You used to think l was funny.
他们杀了Michael
They killed Michael.
我很难过
l'm sorry.
你难过什么?
How sorry are you?
什么?
What?
你这样问什么意思?
What's that supposed to mean?
你怎么了?
What's with you?
你身上有个8的印记
You have the mark of 8 on you.
印记并不表示--
Mark doesn't mean--
你是个骗子
You're a liar.
你和Bethlehem在一起
You were with Bethlehem.
你也是他们的一分子?
Does that make you one of them?
别逼我用这个
Don't make me use this.
起风了
Wind's come up.
越来越冷了
It's getting colder too.
另一场暴风就要来了
Must be another storm.
还要什么?
Anything else?
我不是说要你....
l didn't mean for you to....
你再不下床走动你的腿就要烂掉
Your legs are going to rot off if you don't try to walk.
-我受伤了 -你懒惰!
-l'm hurt. -You're lazy!
懒惰?
Lazy?
我的胃上穿了一个洞...
l got a hole in my stomach...
...而且我很虚弱
...and l'm weak.
这周围只有雪和草...
The  big meals around here are snow and grass...
...而且我们的草就要用完了
...and we're running out of grass.
你要干什么?
What're you doing?
把早餐给我吧!
Give me a break!
我去检查一下关口
l'm going to check the pass.
你为什么这么着急?
Why are you in such a hurry?
我们可以考虑一下更糟的地方
l could think of worse places.
或者更糟的军队
Or l could think of worse company.
好极了!
Perfect!
救命!
Help!
Please!
快来呀!
Quick!
上帝呀, 救救我!
God, help me!
我告诉你了我没事
l told you that's all there was.
正因为如此你该吃了它
That's why you should have it.
我知道你能走
l knew you could walk.
你真奇怪
You're weird.
你知道吗？?
lKnow that?
我曾经在月亮上走过, Abby
We walked on the moon once, Abby.
真的?
So?
但现在有什么好?
What good is that now?
显然你忘记了...
Obviously you've forgotten...
...唐，和...
...Tang and...
...微波炉，还有....
...microwave ovens and....
你的脸看起来很可爱
Your face looks pretty.
我的意思是...
l mean...
...如果没受伤
...not so bruised.
其实...
Look...
...有些事你应该知道
...there's something you'd better know.
你很快就能发现
You're going to find out soon enough.
我怀孕了
l'm pregnant.
是Michael的孩子
lt's Michael's baby.
但其实你才是真正的父亲
You're just the body father.
你怎么知道是我的...
How do you know it's mine...
...不是Bethlehem的?
...not Bethlehem's?
他每天晚上都和我在一起
He tried with me almost every night.
但是他不行...
He couldn't do it...
...所以他打我
...so he beat me.
还说是我的错
Said it was my fault.
对不起, Abby
l'm sorry, Abby.
怎么了?
What is it?
出什么事了?
What's wrong?
是孩子吗?
ls it the baby?
那个关口空了
The pass is clear.
发生了什么事?
What happened?
还好，你把我们的东西搬出来了
Good, you got our stuff out.
当然
Of course.
什么?
What?
我不明白
l don't understand.
火是我放的
l set the fire.
难道你认为我们要永远呆在这里吗?
Did you think we'd stay here forever?
当然不是
No.
如果你能和我一起走 给孩子找一个安全的地方我会很感激的...
l'd appreciate it if you'd walk with me to find someplace safe for the baby...
...否则我们就分开
...then we can split up.
你刮脸了
You shaved.
看起来不错
Looks nice.
你真是很奇怪!
You're really weird!
你知道吗?
You know that?
你听说过Saint Rose吗, Abby?
You ever heard of Saint Rose, Abby?
我听别人说过
l've heard people talk.
我听过很多名字...
l've heard lots of names...
...Bliss, Hesperia, 还有New Eden
...Bliss, Hesperia, and New Eden.
Sheriff Briscoe 说这是幻想
Sheriff Briscoe says it's a fantasy.
他错了
He's wrong.
Saint Rose 就在那里...
Saint Rose is out there...
...我要找到它
...and l'm going to find it.
但你是邮差
But you're the postman.
我谁也不是, Abby
l'm nobody, Abby.
我讨厌这样
This is what l hate.
陌生人
Strangers.
你是对她说 嗨, 还是把她拦下来?
Do you say hi, or do you blow their heads off?
他们到底想分享他们所有的还是夺去你有的?
Do they want to share what they got or take what you have?
如果他们想要夺取,你怎么去阻止他们?
lf they want to take, how far are you willing to go to stop them?
好了, 停在那儿
All right, that's far enough.
我们不想惹麻烦
We don't want any trouble.
我也不想,先生
Me neither, mister.
你是谁?
What are you?
18号邮递员...
Carrier 1 8...
...美国邮政服务
...U.S. Postal Service.
有信吗?
Got any mail?
那不可能
That's impossible.
你没听说过邮差吗?
Ain't you heard of The Postman?
没有
No.
告诉我们
Tell us.
他是幸存的最伟大的人
He's only the greatest man who ever lived.
他穿过荒地...
He crossed the wasteland...
...用拳头把敌人打倒...
...shook his fist at the enemy...
...把口水吐到Bethlehem将军的眼睛里
...and spit in the eye of General Bethlehem himself.
他现在和Starkey总统一起从东边回来了
He's back east with President Starkey right now.
谁告诉你这些?
Who told you all this?
邮局局长Ford Lincoln Mercury
Postmaster Ford Lincoln Mercury.
他亲自参加了重建的国会
He's in direct contact with the restored Congress.
亲自参加?!
Direct contact?!
我不相信!
l don't believe this!
邮递员营地!
Carrier camp!
大家集合!
Gather around, everybody!
快,集合 又来了一封信
Come on, gather around. Got another letter here.
昨晚到的
lt came in last night.
-这儿怎么了? -邮差送给Ford又一封信
-What's all this? -The Postman sent Ford another letter.
他要读了
He's going to read it.
你们好，邮递员们
''Hello, all postal carriers.
我现在在Minneapolis和Starkey总统在一起...
l'm here in Minneapolis with President Starkey...
...但我的心跟你们在一起
...but my thoughts are with you.
请记住...
Remember...
...没有什么值得整晚去做
...nothing worth doing can be done overnight.
抬起你的头尽力别被击中
lKeep your chins up and do your best not to get shot.
你们是...
Signed...
...邮差 !
...The Postman'' !
他的信总是很短
His letters are always kind of short.
等等! 还有一个附言
Hold on! There's a P.S.
有人知道附言代表什么?
Does anybody know what P.S. stands for?
-天哪! -那是H.S., Eddie
-Holy shit! -That would be H.S., Eddie.
当我在Pineview生活时我见过他
No, l saw him once when l lived in Pineview.
它就是邮差
lt's The Postman.
我猜你会说这个
Guess you want to talk about this.
我找到他了! 我找到他了!
l found him! l found him!
Minneapolis?
''Minneapolis?''
P.S. Ford知道做什么?
''P.S. Ford knows what to do?''
这是什么?
What is this?
这都是什么? 这究竟是什么--
What is all this? What the hell--
我撒谎了!
l lied!
我告诉人们你亲自和我联系了
l told people you were in direct contact with me.
-为什么? -因为我不想就这样结束
-Why? -Because l didn't want it to end.
看...
Look...
...我不知道我能呆多久 我是说...
...l don't know how long l can stay. l mean...
...Starkey总统...
...President Starkey...
...他一旦传话给我我又要走
...he's going to send word for me one day and then l'll have to move on.
你明白吗?
Do you understand?
但你一直会呆到他传话来, 对吗?
But you'll stay until he sends word, right?
别这样 把手放下
Don't do that. Hands down.
你会一直呆到Starkey总统传话过来,对吗?
You're staying till President Starkey sends word, right?
对!
Yes!
直到他传话，没错
Until he sends word. Right.
你能说一些话让他们知道真的是你?
Could you say a few words just so they know it's really you?
我就是（邮差）
lt's me.
下来了
Coming down.
我们先把所有信件运到这里
We bring all the mail here first.
分拣
We sort it.
编组 再送出去
We group it. Then it goes out.
到目前为止，我们已经有30条线路了
So far, we got 30 routes.
你把tyranny写错了
You spelled ''tyranny'' wrong.
天哪!
Boy!
他太帅了
He's smart.
快速地完成...
From the swift completion...
...指定的任务
...of their appointed rounds.
祝贺大家，你们现在是美国邮递员了
Congratulations. You are now U.S. postal carriers.
你多大了?
How old are you?
我68了,先生
l'm 68, sir.
我能问你一个问题吗?
Can l ask you a question?
你能骑马吗?
Can you ride?
不能
No.
也不能走太远
Can't walk too good either.
那你为什么要来这里?
So why are you here?
我知道材料学
l know stuff.
你在哪儿刻的?
Where did you get that?
1970年
1 9 70.
一个大眼睛女孩儿...
A girl with eyes as big as saucers...
...在一个叫Saigon的小镇给我刻的
...did me in a little town called Saigon.
Ford让我住他的地方
Ford wants me to have his place.
他说是最好的
Said it's the best.
我在另一边
l'm on the other side.
我在这儿有很多屋子
l got plenty of room here.
和制服一样多
So much for the uniform theory.
他是在Oregon边界被抓住的
He was captured on the Oregon border.
你到底是谁?
Who the hell are you?
12号邮递员
Carrier 1 .
美国邮政服务
United States Postal Service.
我要队伍在拂晓之前动身
l want the camp struck at dawn.
我们将向北行进!
We'll be moving north!
你把tyranny写错了
You spelled ''tyranny'' wrong.
我希望他们停止喝酒
l wish they'd stop saluting.
注意安全
Just stay safe.
记住...
Remember...
...邮递员比邮件重要
...the mailman's more important than the mail.
天哪，他太帅了
Boy, he's smart.
在我小的时候我经常把帽子朝后
When l was a kid we used to turn our hat around backwards.
我认为比较酷
Thought it was cool.
上帝保佑!
Jesus Christ!
该死!
Damn!
我错过了
l missed him.
这个镇叫什么?
What's the name of this town?
我们从来没有给它命名
We never named it.
我宣布...
l officially declare...
...10号邮政所...
...Postal Station Number 1 0...
...在Elvis, Oregon...
...in Elvis, Oregon...
...正式开业
...open for business.
从现在开始你们可以把信件送到下面去，好吗?
From now on you got to get your mail down there, okay?
这个看来不能用了
This one doesn't work.
再读一遍
Read it again.
你确定?
Are you sure?
是的
Yes.
亲爱的妈妈：听到你的消息真是奇迹
''Dearest Mom: What a miracle to hear from you.''
生活在变好
Stuff is getting better.
生活每天都在变好
Stuff is getting better every day.
我不认识你...
l don't know who you are...
...但我知道我错怪你了
...but l do know l was wrong about you.
镇长，你也有一封信
Got a letter for you too, Sheriff.
这是我妹妹来的信
lt's from my sister.
我还以为她死了
Thought she was dead.
你想错了
You thought wrong.
想跳支舞吗?
Would you like to dance?
Well, they say that you can never
Never go back home
And if you're bound to wander
You're bound to be alone
You say I got no right
To feel what I feel
When I look into your eyes
跳个舞好吗?
Want to dance?
But that I dream of you
Most every night
Comes as no surprise
Well, I've been Out on this road for so long
Far and wide
Do I roam
But something in your smile tells me
I'm almost home
I was lost in the dark
All alone
Till the light
In your eyes showed me
I was almost
Home is where the heart is
And my heart goes with you
I would travel till the end of time
If that's what I have to do
Just to spend one night
Till your sweet love light
Come down
Shining down on me
喂喂
Hello.
你在跟谁说话?
Who do you talk to?
试了7年了什么都没有...
Not a soul in 7 years of trying...
...但是我愿意
...but l will.
来点吗?
Want some?
不了，谢谢
No, thanks.
别让孩子看见这些
Don't let the kids see that.
你带个头,看看
You go ahead, take a look.
我是一个航空工程师
l was an aerospace engineer.
我帮助设计了伽利略号宇宙空间站
l helped design the Galileo Space Station.
真的?
No shit?
真的
No shit.
我曾梦想它绕着地球永远转下去...
l dream it's orbiting the Earth forever...
...装着一打死人骨头...
...with a dozen human skeletons...
...对着别人咧着嘴笑...
...all grinning at each other...
...嘲笑我们下面这些人
...laughing at us down here.
-怎么了? -是Tony
-What is it? -lt's Tony.
他迟到了
He's overdue.
那是5号
That makes 5.
所有南方的路线
All on southern routes.
还是孩子
Just children.
你给我的都是孩子
You bring me children.
我要一个男人
l want a man.
我们知道出生和...
We got births and...
...死亡
...deaths.
知道天气 大部分谈话
Got weather. Mostly gossip.
这里什么都没有
There's nothing here.
什么都没有?
Nothing?
所有的...
Everything...
...都在这
...is here.
我是唯一看见这些的?!
Am l the only one who sees that?!
什么?
What?
一个军人,特别是个指挥官...
A military man, especially a commander...
...应该有一本帐
...should keep a journal.
在他死后,这是唯一的防御...
After he's gone, it's the only real defense...
...对付那些后来出现的诽谤
...against the slander that later arises.
告诉我你还知道些什么
Tell me about the other stuff you know.
糟糕!
Shit!
把尸体抬走
Get rid of the bodies.
我不想让这些人怪我们所做的
l don't want these people blamed for what we did.
无论大雪还是暴雨 无论是炎炎烈日还是漆黑夜晚...
Neither snow, nor rain, nor gloom of night...
...穿过强盗的地狱, 穿过战火...
...through bandit's hell, through firefight...
...穿过洪水和瘟疫 我们不能失败...
...through flood and plague we cannot fail...
...什么都不能阻止邮件
...no Holnist trash will stop the mail.
你现在是美国邮递员
You are now U.S. Postal Carriers.
他们修改了誓词
They changed the oath.
Ford的主意
Ford's idea.
身份
Figures.
他们从来没问过他们要取代谁...
They don't think to ask who they're replacing...
...或者为什么
...or why.
先生?
Sir?
如果能和您握手我会感到很光荣的
lt'd be an honor if l could shake your hand.
我认识你吗?
Do l know you?
我想不认识
l don't think so.
好运
Good luck, then.
好孩子
Nice kid.
要不了多久你就没命了
He'll probably be dead in a week.
现在不是你的错
Now that is not your fault.
你已经精疲力尽了，你需要休息 那里有食物--
You're exhausted. You need rest. There's food--
-你去哪儿? -22号路线
-Where are you going? -Route .
你下来 下马
You're grounded. Get off the horse.
你知道规则的
You know the rule.
什么规则?
What rule?
22号太靠近南边了 下马
, it's too far south. Get off the horse.
但是他们在等着--
But they're waiting on--
你快给我下马！
Get off the goddamn horse!
我回来处理的
l'll tie him off to this one.
你不能再这么做了
You can't keep doing this!
-做什么？ -跑所有的线路
-Doing what? -Riding all the routes.
你这样救不了任何人
You're not saving anybody.
我有没有告诉你我怎样成为一个邮差的？
Did l ever tell you how l got to be a postman?
我不知道你是哭还是笑
l don't know if you'd laugh or cry.
那是什么？
What is it?
当心！
Watch out!
着火了，快跑
We got fire! Move!
-邮资欠费 -Elvis巡逻
-''Postage due.'' -Elvis patrol.
你想要挑起战争吗？
You want a war?
你想要挑起战争吗？！
You want a war?!
我就跟你来场...
l'll give you...
硬仗！
...a war!
我就是为战争
l was...
而生！
...born for it!
凶手！
You murderers!
你以为你可以骑马？
You think you can ride?!
那今天就是你的幸运日
Then today's your lucky day!
Bethlehem说...
Bethlehem says...
他会向北进攻
...he's headed north.
他将在每个镇子杀死10个人...
He's going to kill 1 0 people in every town...
再在地上焚烧他们尸体 以此来报复你
...then burn it to the ground for what you did.
他说他会到Pineview去
He said that Pineview's on his way.
他将会在那里等你 但不会等太久
He'd wait there for you, but not for long.
我很害怕
l was so scared, sir.
我以为他们会杀了我
l thought they were going to kill me too.
看见没？
See?
我早告诉过你，我们来得太晚了
We're too late. l told you.
你打算怎么办？
What're you going to do?
我要阻止他们
l'm going to stop this.
你不能
You can't.
你给我让开，都给我让开
Get out of the way, Ford. All of you!
他们会杀了你的
They'll kill you!
拦住他
Hold him!
住手
Stop it!
-你们伤着他了 -没有
-You're hurting him! -l'm not!
伤着了
Yes, you are!
没有，我们没伤害他
l'm not! l'm not hurting him.
这都是因为我 我没有执行你的命令
This is all my doing. l went against your orders.
你叫我埋了那些死尸 但我把他们送到Bethlehem那里了
You told me to bury the dead Holnists, but l sent them Bethlehem.
为什么？
Why?
我们得让Bethlehem知道 我们永不放弃
Bethlehem has to know we won't stop!
真是该死
Goddamn it, Ford!
那些人是因我们而死啊
Those people are dying because of us!
他们因为我们所做的才死的阿
They're dying because of what we did.
不是的 他们是因为Bethlehem才死的
They're not! They're dying because of Bethlehem...
因为这是个狗屎世界 如果我们要想改变它
...because this is a shitty world! lf we're going to change it...
就总会有人要牺牲
...then someone might have to die.
如果我可以替他们在下面受死 我愿意，但我做不到
lf l could make it be me down there, l would, but l can't!
不要啊，求你们了
No! Please!
-你，滚开 -拦住她
-You, out here! -Hold her!
求求你了
Please!
他就在某个地方
He's out there somewhere.
看着我们
Watching.
我能感觉得到
l can feel it.
你也感觉到了，不是吗？
You feel it too, don't you?
镇长，本来大可不必如此
lt didn't have to end like this, Sheriff!
他知道我在哪里 如果他是个男人他就会现身
He knew where l'd be if he wanted to face me like a man!
但他却像个兔子一样
lnstead he's hiding...
躲起来了
...like a rabbit!
你们的邮差也不过如此
So much for your Postman!
中尉！
Lieutenant!
有!
Ready!
我们甚至不知道他们的名字
We don't even know their names.
我知道
We know their names.
那个就是我父亲
l think that's my dad.
瞄准！
Aim!
继续前进阿，邮差！
Ride, Postman!
继续前进！
Ride!
你听见了吗？!
You hear me?!
我叫你们继续前进！
l said, ''Ride!''
射击！
Fire!
天哪，我都干了些什么啊！
My God, what have l done?
Ford所做的是错的
What Ford did was wrong!
但我们却没有采取任何的措施
But it doesn't change anything...
来进行补救，不是吗？
...for any of us, does it?
人都在这了？
ls this everybody?
其余的还在赶路
The rest are on the overdue list.
那就是都在这了
Then this is everybody.
有封来自总统的信
Got a letter from the President.
你们好，邮递员们！
''Greetings, all carriers.''
总统好！
Greetings, President Starkey!
我一直都在和邮差保持联络
''l've been in contact with The Postman.
我收到了所有的报告
And l've received all the reports.
我为你们自豪
l'm proud of you all.
在暗无天日的日子里 在这个黑暗的世界里
ln dark days, in a weary world...
你们付出了所有，却一无所求
...you gave everything and asked for nothing.
你们打退绝望，重拾希望
You beat back despair and replaced it with hope.
而你的国家却无法给你们任何回报
For that, your country can never repay you.
但是付出的代价太大
But the price is too high...
而我也不想再看到我的勇士们有任何的牺牲
...and l won't see any more of my bravest die.
职责所在，我将要解散...
lt is my duty to hereby disband...
重建的美国的邮政服务
...the Postal Service of the Restored United States.
请将你们的制服都烧掉...
You are to burn your uniforms...
而邮差也将立即返回Minneapolis
...and The Postman is to return to Minneapolis at once.
谢谢
Thank you.
上帝保佑你们
And God bless you all.
总统敬上
The President.''
总统从没写过这样的信
The President never wrote that letter.
如果他能写信的话 他就会这么写的
lf he could've, that's what he would have said.
还有一封信是给谁的？
Who's the other letter to?
Bethlehem.
-我早上就把信送过去 -信上说什么？
-l'm taking it to him in the morning. -What's it say?
-内容保密，你知道这是规矩 -信上到底怎么说的？
-Mail's private, you know that. -What does it say?
信上说要结束了
lt says it's over.
就是说我们要放弃了
lt says we quit.
那是你放弃了
lt says you quit!
誓词是怎么说的？
What about the oath?
那你告诉我
Tell me something, Ford.
一个死了的邮递员又能投递几封信呢
How much mail can a dead postman deliver?
都结束了
lt's over.
那让我去送信
Then l'll take it.
我信不过你
l can't trust you.
如果这就是结局...
lf this is the end...
如果这是最后一封投递的信
...if this is the last piece of mail that ever gets delivered...
就让我来发吧
...l'll take it.
无论谁发这封信，都有可能会牺牲
Whoever delivers this letter, Ford, probably dies for it.
我仍然还是个邮差！
l'm still a postman!
你欠我的
You owe it to me.
我也欠我自己的
l owe it to me.
那不能怪Ford
It's not Ford's fault.
他和你不一样，他没有你的那些经历 他们都没有
He's not like you. He doesn't have your memories. None of them do.
这就是他们的全部了
This is all they have.
-这是他们知道的唯一神圣的事 -什么？
-lt's the only decent thing they know. -What?
做个邮差！
Being a postman?
都是胡扯，Abby
lt's all bullshit, Abby.
全是胡扯
All of it.
我穿制服只是为了保暖
l took the uniform off a skeleton to stay warm.
我只是安慰他们而已
l made up the rest to stay fed.
根本没有所谓的...
There is no...
重建的美国
...Restored United States.
我觉得事情就是如此
l figured it was something like that.
我要去Saint Rose
l'm going to Saint Rose.
我带你一起去
l'm taking you with me.
我已经帮你把马准备好了
l've already packed your horse.
我知道你不想听
l know you don't want to hear it...
但是你的腹中有我的孩子
...but that's my child inside you.
我想让他出生在一个安全的地方
l want to see it born somewhere safe.
我想我认出你来了
l thought l recognized you.
Bethlehem将军说当我把枪指着你时 你应该跪倒在地
General Bethlehem said you should be on your knees when l do this.
我才不理那个混蛋说些什么
l don't give a damn what that asshole said.
将军是个了不起的人物
The general is a great man!
将军就他妈的是个疯子
The general is a fucking lunatic.
你想见识一下什么是男子汉？
You want to see a man?
那就是
That's a man.
准备好没？
You ready?
好了
Yes.
你至少要比Bethlehem强些
You're a better man than Bethlehem.
我看得出来
l've seen it.
尊敬的Bethlehem
''To Bethlehem.
这是我的真心话
This letter is my testimony...
事实上并没有
...to the fact that there is no...
重建后的美国
...Restored United States...
也没有什么邮政服务
...and there is no postal service.''
他想让我相信这个？
He expects me to believe this?
这是真的
lt's true.
我当时就在那 他解散了邮递员组织
l was there. He disbanded the carriers...
然后向西边走了
...and rode west.
叛徒！
Traitor!
这么说我赢了
Then l've won.
把我们昨天抓到的那个人带过来 把他们一起处死
Bring the one we found yesterday. They can die together.
叛徒！ 你这个叛徒！
You traitor! You're a traitor!
那个人是那边的二号人物
That one's the second-in-command.
怎么没让我感到惊喜呢？
Why doesn't that surprise me?
我在想，长官...
l was thinking, sir...
对我们来说把他关起来也许更有价值
...he might be more valuable to us as a prisoner.
本打算让你干掉他的
You were supposed to kill him...
对吗？
...weren't you?
但是我没办法靠近他
l couldn't get close enough.
你是谁？
Who are you?
我叫Clark
My name's Clark.
重建后的加州邮递员
Postal Carrier for the Restored Republic of California.
你又是谁？
Who are you?
邮局局长，Ford
Postmaster Ford Lincoln Mercury.
万分荣幸！
lt's an honor.
等一等
Wait!
等一等，先别开火
Wait a minute. Hold your fire.
你们俩并不认识？
You two don't know each other?
这将不会结束
This'll never be over.
会一直持续下去
lt'll go on.
除非我是在和一个该死的鬼魂在战斗
Except l'll be fighting a goddamn ghost.
-可以开枪了吗？ -别开枪，该死的
-Should we fire, sir? -No, goddamn it!
我不会和鬼魂打仗
l won't fight a ghost.
Tabula...
...rasa...
...先生们
...gentlemen.
一段清白的历史
A clean slate.
我要对所有的邮递员穷追猛打
l want all mail carriers hunted down.
我一定要找到那个邮差
l want The Postman found.
我要狠狠地打击他
l want him dealt with.
上校，集合部队
Colonel, organize the scouts.
你说他往西走了？
You said he rode west?
而这是他的二号人物？
And this is his second-in-command?
是的，长官
Yes, sir!
我会留你一条命用来谈判 要让邮差投鼠忌器
l'll keep you to bargain with. The Postman is weak that way.
把枪扔到地上
Set your rifle on the ground!
扔到地上
Set it on the ground.
什么？这个破玩意？
What? This old thing?
子弹都没上上去呢
lt isn't even loaded.
我们这是在哪里？
Where are we?
你们在大桥城
You're in Bridge City...
而这里不允许枪支
...where we don't allow guns.
岗哨说你要来了
The sentry said you were coming.
我知道你，你...
l know you. You're...
...很出名
...famous.
曾经是...
l was once...
...有那么...
...sort of...
一点点
...kind of.
不再是了
Not anymore.
你们要穿过去？
Looking to cross?
是的
We will be.
但现在我们想要一些吃的
Right now we'd appreciate some food.
没问题
Okay.
在我们后面，还有几个孩子
There are some kids behind us.
几个？
How many?
3个
3.
3个，好吧
3. Okay.
进来吧，孩子们
Come on in, guys!
我知道你们就在那
l know you're out there.
-等等，等一等 -他想要什么？
-Wait. Just wait. -What did he want?
请安静，他说...
Hold on. He says...
...他在寻找邮差
...he's looking for The Postman.
再没有这样一回事了
There's no such thing anymore.
但那个骑马的人说有这么一回事
The man on the horse says there is.
他认为邮差就在这里
He thinks he's here.
而他会带着他的同伙再回来
And he's coming back with friends.
邮差时干吗的？
What's a postman?
你从来没听说过邮差？
You never heard of a postman?
你就是那个邮差？
Are you The Postman?
对
Yeah.
伙计，我听说过你啊
l heard of you, man.
你很出名
You're famous.
也许，是吧
Yeah, l guess l am.
但突然之间 我已经...
And all of a sudden, l'm not...
...不再是个邮差了
...wearing the right clothes.
伙计，你会喜欢上这玩意的
Man, you're going to love this!
打开第二道瀑布
Open that second chute, bro!
邮差先生，你很有天赋
You have a gift, Postman.
在Pineview，我看见它又回来了
l saw it back in Pineview.
你给了我们都已经遗忘了的宝贵财富
You've given us all back what we'd forgotten.
你让March觉得她仿佛重见光明
You made Mrs. March feel like she could see again.
你让Ford觉得他就是这个世界的一分子
You made Ford feel like he was part of the world.
你给了我们希望...
You give out hope like it was...
...就像点亮你口袋里的蜡烛
...candy in your pocket.
你还记得这个吗？
Remember this?
我记得
l remember.
我常想，你是故意把这个留给我的
l always like to think that you left it on purpose.
这对我来说很不容易
This is hard for me.
Michael是我见过的最好的男人
Michael was the best man l ever knew.
我从来没想过 我会像爱他那样去爱另外一个人
l never thought there'd be another man l could love the way l loved him.
我没法看得那么远
l couldn't see it for so long.
而你现在就要离开
And now you're leaving.
我害怕
And l'm afraid.
我害怕你再也找不到你的Saint Rose
l'm afraid you'll never find your Saint Rose.
这不重要
lt's not important.
我害怕你再也看不到你的小孩
l'm afraid you'll never see your baby.
我需要充足的电源！ 这个家伙要走很远的路呢！
l need full power, man! This dude's got a long way to go!
这机器运转得真他妈的完美
This thing's working perfect, man!
比看起来还要高很多，不是吗？
A lot higher than it looks, huh?
你差点就报销了
You nearly went.
快进来吧
Get in.
在前面有三个规模很大的镇子
There's 3 good-sized towns up ahead...
如果你能说服他们跟你走 你就能找到足够的帮手
...with enough people to help you if you can convince them to come.
不要告诉任何人
Don't tell anybody...
说我喜欢玩这玩意，仅仅因为它好玩
...l like to ride this damn thing just for the hell of it.
你知道，作为一个领导 我得注意自身形象
Being a city official has its perks, you know?
相信我吧，伙计 这会让你更快的
Trust me, man. This'll get you there a lot faster.
我怎么停下来呢？
How do l stop?
别再这里婆婆妈妈了
Quit worrying about the little things.
祝你好运，跑得飞快！
Good luck, and Godspeed.
长官，我向您报告！
Reporting for duty, sir!
-知道该怎么做吗？ -去说服人们
-Know what to do? -Talk to the people.
告诉他们这很重要
Tell them it's important.
告诉他们我们可以做到
Tell them we can make a difference.
再向前冲，亲爱的朋友们 再向前冲
''Once more unto the breach, dear friends, once more...
...或者以死守卫我们的城墙
...or close the wall with our dead!
在和平时期，我们要谦虚彬彬有礼
In peace, nothing so becomes a man as modesty and humility.
但是一旦爆发战争
But when the blast of war blows in our ears...
我们就要像头猛虎一样勇猛
...then imitate the action of the tiger.
鼓起我们的勇气 收起我们温和的本性...
Summon up the blood. Disguise fair nature with rage...
去和敌人拼个你死我活
...and lend the eye a terrible aspect. ''
-他们是谁？ -不知道
-Who are they? -l don't know.
在我看来大部分都是老弱病残
Looks like mostly women and young people to me.
有多少？
How many?
那是一支军队
lt's an army.
终于...
At last...
还是有人鼓起用来和我作战了
...someone with courage enough to bring the fight to me.
先生们，算总账的时候到了
Reckoning, gentlemen!
他们看起来热血沸腾
They're an eager-looking bunch!
士气真的是很重要
Morale is a dangerous thing.
把俘虏带上来
Bring up the prisoner!
让我们来告诉他们 游戏该怎么来玩
We'll show them how this game is played.
呆在这
Stay here.
他在投降？
ls he surrendering?
该死，我不希望这样
God, l hope not.
小小搬运工
My little shipping clerk.
卖复印机的销售员
Mr. copy-machine salesman.
我们俩是一对大骗子
We're both a couple of frauds.
说的没错
So be it.
但是一个伟人是由另一个伟人来成就的
But great men are made by other great men.
Rommel成就了Patton
Patton had Rommel.
Lee成就了Grant
Grant had Lee.
而你将会成就我的霸业
But l get you.
你不是将军
You're no general.
你甚至也不是一个好的画家
You're not even a good painter.
你想要激将我？
Trying to goad me into a fight?
如果战争由发起它的人来结束，就非常完美
lt'd be great if wars were fought just by the assholes who started them.
我们可以对这场战争作个了结
We could settle this right here...
只有你跟我
...you and me.
不幸的是，这种方法行不通
Unfortunately, it doesn't work that way.
但是在你的部队里却可以
But it does in your army.
我引用八大法律中的...
l invoke Law Seven...
...第七条
...of the Laws of Eight!
在部队里谁都可以挑战老大的位子
''Any man may challenge for leadership of the clan!''
我向你挑战
l challenge you.
你不是我们一伙的，你没有这个权力
You're not a Holnist. You're not a member. You don't have the right.
我拥有所有的权力
l have every right!
我引用第七条法律
l invoke Law Seven.
你去哪...?
Where...?
我要挑战...
l challenge...
...老大的位子
...for leadership of the clan!
我在哪里见过你？
Where do l know you from?
你下令抢劫...
''Cry havoc...
...然后喂养这些战争走狗
...and let slip the dogs of war!''
你还记得那些吗？
You remember that?
莎士比亚
Shakespeare.
那个不想打仗的人
The one who didn't want to fight.
那时我就应该设法杀死你 但你看起来太强大
l should have found a way to kill you then, but you seemed so strong.
第七条法律...
Law Seven...
...那就是
...it is!
这场战争将在这里作个了结
This war is settled here!
我研究过人们
l studied people.
我知道你的问题在哪
l know your problem.
你知道...
Do you know...
为什么你不能打吗？
...why you can't fight?
因为你不知道为何而战
Because you have nothing to fight for.
你什么也不关心
You don't care about anything.
你什么也不在乎
You don't value anything.
你对什么都不信任
You don't believe in anything!
而那些却让我变得更厉害
And that's what makes me better.
我信任...
l believe...
...美国
...in the United States.
我们本可以不这样的
lt doesn't have to be this way.
我们本可以不用互相残杀
We don't have to kill each other.
第三条法律...
''Law Three:
仁慈...
Mercy...
...是留给弱者的
...is for the weak.''
Ford，不要
Ford, don't!
第八条法律
''Law Eight:
只有一种惩罚...
There's only one penalty...
...而那就是死
...and that penalty is death.''
他不值得的
He isn't worth it.
现在我是部队的头儿
l'm the head of the clan now!
将会产生新的法律
There are going to be new laws!
第一条：
Law One:
不再杀戮
No more killing.
我们将拥有和平
There's going to be peace!
你觉得这样如何？
How about it, Ford Lincoln Mercury?
Ford，要像个领袖的样子
Be a leader, Ford.
第八条法律
Law Eight:
活着...
Live...
...就好好活
...and let live.
你爸爸写信来说
Your daddy wrote to tell you...
他会尽快赶回来的
...he'll be here as soon as he can...
他非常爱你
...and that he loves you very much.
信件太慢了
Mail's slow.
我打算亲自来告诉她
l'm going to have to see about that.
你的女儿
Your daughter.
她的名字叫希望
Her name is Hope.
我父亲看到我们是如此的脆弱...
My father saw how fragile we are...
...如此轻易的就落入暴君的统治
...and how quickly we fell into the hands of tyranny.
他发现普通人...
He saw that ordinary men...
...也可以有潜力可挖，可以找到勇气
...could reach deep within themselves and find courage.
他发现如果我们作为一个国家来沟通...
He saw that if we began to communicate as a nation...
...我们就可以再一次强大起来
...we could become strong again...
团结起来
...united.
但是他从来没有真正见到过Saint Rose
But he never did see Saint Rose.
他说...
He said...
...还有太多的事情要去做
...there was too much to be done.
他许下承诺
He'd made a promise.
他信守承诺 追逐一个又一个的梦想
And in keeping it, he traded one dream for another.
无怨无悔
With no regrets.
所以，为了向我的父亲表示敬意....
And so, in honor of my father....
那个小孩是我
That was me.
“邮差” -=结束=-